A Guide to the Records of the Office of the Vice President for Administration, Stuart K. Cassell, 1945-1975
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- 1969
  - Harrison, W.B. – Research Division (2 folders) (Box 32, Folder 24-25)
  - Heterick, R.C.- Computer Center, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - King, H.P. Jr.- Dining Halls, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Montgomery, J.R.- Institutional Research, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Moseley, F.O.- Athletic Association, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Nickols, I.E.- Security, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Russell, G.E.- Alumni Affairs (2 folders), 1969 (Box 32, Folder 31-32)
  - Shirk, F.C.- Librarian, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Shotts, J.L.- Purchasing, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Sterrett, William M.- Buildings and Grounds (2 folders), 1969 (Box 32, Folder 35-36)
  - Strother, W.H.- Information Services (2 folders), 1969 (Box 32, Folder 37-38)
  - Vandenberg, H.P.C.- Physical Plant Plan, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Art Commission, Floyd E. Johnson, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Attorney General Virginia, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - C- Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Capital Outlay Progress Report, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Civilian Interdorm Council, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Donaldson Brown Center, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - D- Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - E- Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - F- Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Fireworks Display, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - G-Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - H-Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Dr. T. Marshall Hahn, Jr. (4 folders), 1969 (Box 33, Folder 14-17)
  - Handbook- Classified Personnel (4 folders), 1969 (Box 33, Folder 18-21)
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - I- Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - J- Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - K- Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Kidder, Peabody and Co., 1969 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - L-Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Chas. Lunsford Sons and Izard (2 folders), 1969 (Box 33, Folder 28-29)
  - Mc- Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - M- Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Marion College, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Military Army and Air Force, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - N- Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - National Associations of Land Grant Universities and Colleges, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - National Association of College and Universities (NACUBO), 1969 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - National Science Foundation, NSF, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - O-Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - New Student Orientation, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Orientation, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Overtime, Authorized, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - P-Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Alfred C. Payne, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - R- Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Revenue Bonds- Dorms and Dining Halls, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - S-Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Sanitation Authority, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Scholarships, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1969-01-31 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1969-02-28 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1969-03-31 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1969-04-30 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1969-05-31 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1969-06-30 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1969-07-31 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1969-08-31 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1969-09-30 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1969-10-31 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1969-11-30 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1969-12-31 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - State Council of Higher Education, Prince B. Woodard, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - State Technical Services, R.C. Smith, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Allen Sowder- Attorney, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Virginia Associated Research Center, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Student Aid Association, H.M. McEver, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Student Budget Board, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Student Correspondence, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Student Government Association (2 folders), 1969 (Box 34, Folder 33-34)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute- Student Programs Incorporated, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - T- Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Tech Festival, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Student Union Board, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - U-V Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - W- Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Water Authority, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - X- Y-Z Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, Joseph F. James, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Division of Budget- L.M. Kuhn (4 folders), 1969 (Box 35, Folder 2-5)
  - Division of Engineering and Buildings- H.D. Hamner Jr. (2 folders), 1969 (Box 35, Folder 6-7)
  - Department of Community Colleges, Dana B. Hamel, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Comptroller, Sidney C. Day, Jr., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - State Corporation Commission- Division of Aerospace Engineering, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Governor, Carter O. Lowance, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Division of Personnel- John W. Garber, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Property Records and Insurance- Stewart R. Moore, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Department of Purchases and Supply- G. Lloyd Nunnally, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Department of Treasury- Lewis H. Vaden, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Division State Planning and Community Affairs, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - State Highway Department, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises and University Services, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Facilities, Inc (3 folders), 1969 (Box 68, Folder 8-10)
- 1970
  - A- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - B-Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - S.K. Cassell- Personal, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Applications, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Blanket Letters, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Budget, Miscellaneous Items, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Bulletins-Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Commission of Student Affairs, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Studies- Malpass, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Building Committee, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Commence Committee, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Commission on Faculty Affairs, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Commission on Research and Graduate Studies, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Faculty Senate, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Forums Board, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Grievance Committee, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Library Committee, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Radiation Safety Committee, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Student Health Services Communication, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Scholarships and Student Aid, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Traffic Committee, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - University Council (8 folders), 1970 (Box 35, Folder 39-41, Box 36, Folder 1-5)
  - Hahn, Dr. T. Marshall (11 folders), 1970 (Box 36, Folder 6-16)
  - Dean James W. Dean (5 folders), 1970 (Box 36, Folder 17-21)
  - Brown, J. Gordon, Dean- Student Services, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Bull, F.W. Graduate School, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Burchard, C.H.- Architecture, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Dean J.W., Vice President-Student Affairs, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Harder, Martha B.,Dean- Men and Women's Residence Programs, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Harper, Laura J.- Home Economics, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Hereford, Karl T., Dean- College of Education, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Harvard, William C. – Arts and Sciences, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Lacy, M.P.- Admissions and Records, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Lavery, W.E., Vice President-Finance, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - McKeefery, W.J., Executive Vice President (2 folders), 1970 (Box 37, Folder 6-7)
  - Malpass, L.F. Vice President- Academic Affairs (2 folders), 1970 (Box 37, Folder 8-9)
  - Martin, E.J. –Agriculture, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Mitchell, H.H. – College of Business, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Skelton, W.E.- Extension, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Ryland, Walter H., 1970 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Torgersen, Paul E.- Engineering, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Bell, Wilson B. – Development, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Boone, J.F. –Treasurer, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Burke, Carl E.- Chief Accountant, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Cato, W.H.- Placement, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Butt, A.T. – Personnel, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Evans, E.B. – Business Manager, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Hardy, J.E.- Student Housing, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Heterick, R.C.- Computing Center, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - King, H.P.- Food Services, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Montgomery, J.R.- Institutional Research, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Moseley, F.O.- Athletic Association, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Nickols, I.E.- Security, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Wilson, Coyt T., Research- Acting, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Russell, G.E.- Alumni Association, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Shirk, F.C.- Librarian, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Shotts, J. L. – Purchasing, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Smoot, R.D. Jr.- Administration Intern, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Sterrett, W.M- Buildings and Grounds (4 folders), 1970 (Box 37, Folder 32-35)
  - Strother, W.H. – Information Services (4 folders), 1970 (Box 37, Folder 36-39)
  - Vandenberg, H.P.C- Physical Plant Planning, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Art Commission- Floyd E. Johnson, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Attorney General Virginia- Andrew P. O'Niller, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - B- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Department of Community Colleges- Dana B. Hamel, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - State Highway Department, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - C- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - S.K. Cassell- Personal, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - D- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Department of Treasury- Walter W. Craigie, Jr., 1970 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Division of Budget, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - E- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Division of Engineering, H.D. Hamner, Jr., 1970 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Comptroller, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Governor- L. Holton, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Division of Personnel- John W. Garber, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Property Records and Insurance- Steward R. Moore, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Department of Purchases and Supplies, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Applications, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Bailey Research Trust (2 folders), 1970 (Box 38, Folder 21-22)
  - Blanket Letters, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Town of Blacksburg, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Capital Outlay-Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Disruptive Activities- Drillfield, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Donaldson Brown Center, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Fireworks Display, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - G- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - H- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Handbook- Personnel, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Horse Barn- Extension Division, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Files in Storage- Tunnel and Backroom, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - F- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - I- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - J- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - K- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - L- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Chas. Lunsford Sons and Izard (2 folders), 1970 (Box 38, Folder 41-42)
  - Mc- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - M- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Mail Handling (2 folders), 1970 (Box 38, Folder 45-46)
  - Military Army and Air Force- General Pachler, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - Motor Pool Operations, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 48)
  - N- Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (2 folders), 1970 (Box 38, Folder 50, Box 39, Folder 1)
  - National Science Foundation, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - O-Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Orientation, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Overtime, Authorized, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - P-Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Patent Policy, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Patent Programs, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Alfred C. Payne, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Physical Examinations, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - R- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Research Corporation, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - VPI Research Park, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Revenue Bonds- Dorms and Dining Halls 1968, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - S-Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Southern Association of College and Universities Business Officers, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Sanitation Authority, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Allen Sowder- Attorney, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Scholarships, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1970-01-31 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1970-02-28 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1970-03-31 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1970-04-30 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1970-05-31 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1970-06-30 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1970-07-31 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1970-08-31 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1970-09-30 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1970-10-31 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1970-11-30 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Student Correspondence, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Student Aid Association, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Student Budget Board, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Student Forums Board, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Student Government Association, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Student Union Board, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - T- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Tech Festival, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - U-V Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - VPI Facilities Inc, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - W- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - VPI Student Programs Inc, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Water Authority, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Ad hoc Communication- Rescue Squad (2 folders), 1971 (Box 39, Folder 44-45)
  - Commission on Faculty Affairs, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - University Services and Auxiliary Enterprise, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- 1971
  - Ad hoc Committee- Fundraising and Self Help Enterprises, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Board of Visitors, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - Building Committee, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 48)
  - Commencement Committee, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - Commission on Faculty Affairs, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 50)
  - Commission for Student Affairs, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 51)
  - Commission on Research and Graduate Studies, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 52)
  - Faculty Senate, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 53)
  - Library Committee, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 54)
  - Radiation Safety Committee, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 55)
  - Traffic Committee, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 56)
  - Brown, J. Gordon- Dean of Student Services (2 folders), 1971 (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
  - Bull, Fred W. –Graduate School, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Burchard, Charles- Architecture, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Dean, James W.- Vice President of Student Affairs (6 folders), 1971 (Box 40, Folder 5-10)
  - Hahn, T. Marshall Jr. (6 folders), 1971 (Box 40, Folder 11-16)
  - Harder, Martha B.- Dean of Men and Women's Residence Programs, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Harper, Laura Jane- Dean of Home Economics, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Harvard, William C.- Dean of Arts and Sciences, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Hereford, Carl T.- College of Education, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Lacy, M.P, Dean- Admissions and Records, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Lavery, W.E., Vice President-Finance, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - McKeefery, W.J., Vice President-Executive (2 folders), 1971 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
  - Malpass, L.F., Vice President- Student Affairs (2 folders), 1971 (Box 41, Folder 3-4)
  - Martin, J.E., Dean- Agriculture, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Bell, Wilson B., Dean –University Development, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Mitchell, H.H., Dean- Business, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 7A)
  - Robertson, Randall M., Dean- Research, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 7B)
  - Ryland, W.H., General Counsel, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Skelton, W.E., Extension, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Torgersen, Paul E., Dean- Engineering, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Boone, J.F.- Treasurer, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Burke, Carl E.- Chief Accountant, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Butt, A.T.- Personal, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Cato, W.H.- Placement, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Evans, E.B. – Business Manager, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Heterick, R.C.- Computing Center, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - King, Howard P.- Food Services, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Montgomery, J.R.- Institutional Research, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Moseley, F.O.- Athletic Association, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Nickols, I.E., Security (2 folders), 1971 (Box 41, Folder 20-21)
  - Rudolph, G.A. – Librarian, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Russell, G.E.- Alumni Office, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Schiffert, C.W. – Infirmary, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Shotts, J.L. –Purchasing, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Smoot, R.D. Jr., Administration Intern, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Sterrett, M.W. – Buildings and Grounds (2 folders), 1971 (Box 41, Folder 27-28)
  - Strother, W.H.- Information Services and other (2 folders), 1971 (Box 41, Folder 29-30)
  - Special Authorizations (3 folders), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 1-3)
  - Vandenberg, H.P.C, Physical Plant Planning, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Art Commission, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Attorney General of Virginia-Andrew P. Miller, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts- Joseph F. James, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Governor- A. Linwood Holton, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Division of Budget- John R. McCutcheon, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Division of Engineering, H.D. Hamner, Jr., 1971 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - State Highway Department, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Division of Personnel, John W. Garber, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Department of Purchases and Supply, Benjamin P. Alsop, Jr., 1971 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Property Records and Insurance, Steward R. Moore (2 folders), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 15-16)
  - A- Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Applications, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - B- Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Bailey Research Trust, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Blacksburg- Town of, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Blanket Letters, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Budget-Miscellaneous Items, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Building Lockup, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - C- Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Capital Outlay Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Cadet Corps- Strengthening, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Caribbean Canadian Chemical Company, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Cassell, S.K.- Personal, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Coliseum Repairs- Baseball, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Coliseum Repairs- Coach Coffey, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Coliseum Repairs- Rug Club, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Coliseum Repairs- Weight Room, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Crawford, A.W.- Business Manager, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Cupp Tool Corporation- Research Park, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - D- Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Disruptive Activities/Security, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Donaldson Brown Center, M.C. Heckel, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - E- Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Economic Stabilization Task Force, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances (2 folders), 1971-01-01-1971-12-31 (Box 42, Folder 42-43)
  - F- Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Federal Mogul Corporation, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Fireworks Display, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - First National Bank Exchange, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Federal Insurance Contributions Act-Retirement System, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - G-Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Management Company, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - H-Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - J-Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - K- Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - L-Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Mc-Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - M-Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Motor Pool Operations, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Chas. Lundsford and Sons (3 folders), 1971 (Box 43, Folder 17-19)
  - N- Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - National Association of State University's and Land Grant Colleges, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - National Association of Colleges and University Business Officers, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - National Science Foundation, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - O-Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Orientation, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Overtime, Authorized, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Military, General Pachler, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - P-Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Patents, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Alfred C. Payne, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Physical Examinations, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Research Park, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Reston, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Reynolds Homestead, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - R- Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - S-Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Sanitation Authority, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Scholarships, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Student Services and Facilities Booklet, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Southern Association of College and Business Officers, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Stadium Donations, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - Stadium Fund Pledges- Paid in Full, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Student Correspondence, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Site Plan Updating, Master, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - Student Government Association- General, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Student Aid Association, H.H. McEver, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Student Union Board, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - T-Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - VPI Facilities Inc (2 folders), 1971 (Box 44, Folder 4-5)
  - VPI Student Programs Inc (3 folders), 1971 (Box 44, Folder 6-8)
  - U-V Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Water Authority, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - W-Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - X-Y-X Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Computer Science Application Proposal, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - University Council, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - University Council Meeting, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Proposal for Doctor of Philosophy Degree, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Proposed Ph.D. Degree in General Psychology, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 17)